redbooks.com 2011-11-22

# Red Books Privacy Policy: Advertising Redbooks.com™

1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy discloses and covers all of the privacy practices of Red Books LLC (“Red Books” or the “Company”), including as they relate to Red Books’s website and related services (collectively, the “Site”).  In this Privacy Policy, “we”, “us”, “our” and other similar references mean Red Books and “you” and “your” and other similar references mean a specific user of the Site.

We understand and respect the privacy concerns of our users, and we have made it a critical focus of the Site to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information you provide us.  We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about how we collect, use and share your personal information, and our privacy practices in general.

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.   BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE.**

2\. The Information We Collect

We may collect two types of information: Personally Identifiable Information (“ _PII_ ”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“ _Non-PII_ ”).

PII is information that identifies a specific user of the Site.  When you engage in certain activities on the Site, such as when you register to use the Site, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself that we will collect and store.  You do not have to engage in the activities in which we ask you to provide such information.  But if you choose to do so, we may ask you to provide certain personal information, such as your first and last name, gender, email address and date of birth.  Depending on what activity you are engaged in, some of the information that we request will be identified as mandatory or as voluntary.  If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

Non-PII is information that identifies your computer and its navigational patterns through the Site (but not a specific user).  We may automatically collect Non-PII information when you visit the Site, through the use of a variety of tools including cookies (small text files that are stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes and which contains information about that user’s computer), or other available data analysis or collection technologies.

3\. How We Use and Share Information

We use the information we collect to (a) provide the services you request; (b) notify you of promotions, special events, new services and special offers; (c) improve our product offerings, customer service and overall experience; (d) improve the content, operation, appearance and utility of the Site; (e) conduct surveys, research and evaluations; (f) troubleshoot and resolve disputes; (g) gather demographic data and (h) accomplish other administrative tasks.

We may share your information collected on the Site with our subsidiaries and other affiliated companies, and with other vendors and business partners, including marketing partners, with whom we work (collectively, “Our Affiliates”).  This includes companies who provide business services to us or on our behalf such as to market products or services to you, monitor Site activity, serve Site content, help to maintain our customer database, administer e-mails, surveys or other contests.  We also reserve the right to disclose your information in good faith as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, with any person or entity that has acquired all or any part of our business or assets, and where needed to prevent fraud and to protect the safety, property, or legal rights of users of the Site or Our Affiliates.

4\. Unsubscribe or Opt Out

If you decide that you are no longer interested in receiving email communications from us, you may follow the instructions in our emails to unsubscribe from our email list or send us an email at info@redbooks.com.

5\. Privacy Policies of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use, storage and disclosure of information that we collect from you.  Other websites, such as websites you may have clicked-on that directed you to the Site or websites that may be accessible to you by clicking-through the Site, have their own privacy policies regarding data collection, use and disclosure practices.  If you visit any such website, we encourage you to review that website’s privacy policy.  We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

6\. Editing and Requesting Your Information

We will permit you to change your profile settings.  Even after you change or remove information from your profile, copies of your information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others or it was copied or stored by other users.  We may also be required to retain your information by law or for legitimate business purposes, such as to prevent identity theft or other misconduct.

We will permit you to request a copy of your PII that we have collected about you by contacting the Company at the address below.  You can also correct factual inaccuracies in this information by contacting the Company.

7\. Storage and Security

We believe the security of your information is a serious issue and we are committed to protecting the information we receive from you.  We use commercially reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control.  Notwithstanding such measures, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Site.  We also are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

8\. Public Forums

You acknowledge and agree that all discussion for ratings, comments, bulletin board service, chat rooms and/or other message or communication facilities on the Site (collectively, “Public Forums”) are public and not private communications, and others may read your communications without your knowledge.  We do not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Public Forum, and, therefore, we specifically disclaim any liability concerning Public Forums and any claims or injuries resulting from your participation in any Public Forum, including any objectionable content.  Generally, any communication which you post to the Site (whether in chat rooms, discussion groups, message boards or otherwise) is considered to be non-confidential.  If particular web pages permit the submission of communications that will be treated by us as confidential, that fact will be stated on those pages.

By posting comments, messages or other information (collectively, “Material”) on the Site or any Public Forum, you irrevocably grant us a non-exclusive, fully paid-up, royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual right and license to use, copy, modify, adapt, publish, translate and distribute such Material (in whole or in part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or technology now known or hereafter developed for the full term of any copyright that may exist in such Material, without territorial or time limitations, and to sublicense such rights through multiple tiers of sublicensees, and you represent and warrant that, if you are not the owner of such Material, that the owner of such Material has expressly granted you the right to grant the foregoing license to Red Books.  You acknowledge and agree that any other user may access, view, store or reproduce the material for that user’s personal use, and that you shall have no recourse against us for any alleged or actual infringement or misappropriation of any proprietary right in your communications to us.  You further grant Red Books the right to use, copy, modify, adapt, publish, translate and distribute any other Material that you make available on or through the Site.

9\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues

We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known by us to be under the age of 13, and no part of the Site is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.  Children under the age of 18 may only use the Site under the supervision and direction of a parent or legal guardian.  Minors under the age of 13 should not use the Site.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us.

10\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time.  The revised Privacy Policy will be effective immediately when posted on the Site.  It is the responsibility of each user to review the Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of the Site after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us at [legal@redbooks.com](mailto:legal@redbooks.com) or contact us at Red Books LLC, PO Box 1514, Summit, NJ 07902.  For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

Initial Version Posted: December 9, 2010
